Guide to the Office of Sponsored Research records, 1942-1996 RG0038
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Manuals and programs, 1963-1977; RG0038 Series 3; 0.5 Linear foot
  This series consists of cost reimbursement contracting manuals, and a program for the 10th Annual Government Contracts Institute at George Washington University. They are arranged chronologically. The material dates from 1963-77, and was accessioned as part of project to clear the backlog in 2001.
  This series has a container list in electronic form, please ask staff for assistance.
  - Government Contracts Institute, 05/02/1963-05/03/1963; RG0038 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Government Contracts Cost, 1977; RG0038 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cost Reimbursement Contracting, 1974; RG0038 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cost Reimbursement Contracting, 1977; RG0038 Series 3 (Box 1, Box 4)
- Project files for schools, departments, programs, ca.1970-85; RG0038 Series 4; 15 Linear feet
  This series consists of sponsored research project files from various schools, departments, and programs. These include the School of Education, School of Engineering, Medical School, National Law Center, logistics program, and University Library. They are arranged chronologically. The material dates from the 1970's and 1980's, and was transferred to University Archives by the Director of Sponsored Research in 1987.
  - Chemistry [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chemistry [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Computers, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Counseling Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Division of Experimental Programs, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ecometric Research [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ecometric Research [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Education, School of, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Education of the Handicapped Policy Project, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Energy Program, Office of, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Engineering [1/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Engineering [2/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Engineering [3/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Psychology, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    #91 through to the end
  - Regional Rehabilitation Research Institute, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    1 through to the end
  - Rehabilitation Research and Training, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Religion, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Science Communication Division, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Medical School and Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    50-118
  - Medical School and Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    119-159
  - Medical School and Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    160-203
  - Medical School and Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    204-236
  - Slavic Languages, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Social Research Group, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Through 18
  - Social Research Group, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    19 through to end
  - Social Research Group: Education Division, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sociology, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Special Education, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    #1-8
  - Operational and Demographic Analysis, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Oral History Program, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Philosophy Dept: GW Research File, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Physics, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    #1-17
  - Physics, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    #18-66
  - Physics, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    #67
  - Political Science, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    #1-19
  - Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Political Science, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    #20 through to end
  - Population Research, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Program of Policy Studies, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    1-40
  - Program of Policy Studies, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    41 through to end
  - Psychology, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    #1-48
  - Psychology, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    #49-90
  - Medical School and Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    #237-315
  - Medical School and Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    #316-443
  - Medical School and Center, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    #370-453
  - American Civilization Studies, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Anthropology, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Biochemistry, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Biology [1/2], undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Biology [2/2], undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Biostatistics, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Biostatistics Center, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Career Services, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Center for Family Research, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Center for Museum Education, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry [1/5], undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Chemistry [2/5], undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Chemistry [3/5], undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - National Law Center, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Music, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Media Analysis Project, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Formerly Mid-East Regional Resource Center, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    #1-3
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Formerly Mid-East Regional Resource Center, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    #4
  - National Exercise and Heart Disease Project, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Natural Resources Policy Center, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Empty
  - Neurobiology Research Training Program, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Nutrition Research Project, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Logistics, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Management Science, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Marvin Center, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Manpower Research Project, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Manpower Research Project #2, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bonato, Roland R: Maternal-Infant Health Computer Project, 12/31/1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Final Report
  - Maternal-Infant Health Computer Project Progress Report, 06/30/1967 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Medical School, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    #1-35
  - Medical School, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    #36-49
  - Experimental Humanities, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Forensic Science, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Geochemistry, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Geography, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Geology, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - German, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Government and Business, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Program in Museum Studies, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Program in STPP, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Health Care Administration, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Health Services Administration, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Health Staff Seminar, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - History, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Human Kinetics and Leisure Studies, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - HumRRO GW Research File, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Special Education #8, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Special Education, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Speech and Drama Department, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Sponsored Research, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - State and Local Finance Project, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Total Investment Project, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - TV News Study Program, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Student Health Service, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - University Library, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Urban and Regional Planning, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Women's Studies, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Workshop for Careers in the Arts, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - English, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - ERIC Clearinghouse, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Project files for programs and institutes, 1950-1982; RG0038 Series 5; 10 Linear feet
  This series consists of sponsored research project files from various schools and programs. These include biological sciences, driver behavior, Policy Studies in Science and Technology, Institute for Educational Leadership, Social Research Group, Education Research Project, Medical Center, manpower research, Program in Science, Technology and Public Policy, army logistics, special education, logistics, and ERIC Clearinghouse. They are arranged chronologically by subject. The materials range in date from 1962-76, and were was added to the University Archives collections from a backlog in 2003.
  - Grant writing handbooks, 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Grant writing handbook: College of Engineering Research Division, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Policies and Procedures
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Annotated Bibliography, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Final Report and Supplement, 09/15/1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Evaluation of Two Driver Improvement Programs
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Basic Frequency Tables for the 5-Point Study, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Part B
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Progress Report-Parent Adolescent Study, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: A Portable Low-Cost Clinic for Traffic Violators, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Perceptual Analysis of the Driving Task, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: A New Approach to Driver Education: Programmed Learning, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Programming Programmers, 04/1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    A Linear Graph Model
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Statistical Study of the Characteristics of DC Driving Population, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Motivations for Safe Driving, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Perceptual Analysis of the Driving Task, 01/1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Driving Skill and its Measurement, 04/1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: A Factor Study of Drivers' Attitudes, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Changing Driver Attitudes through Group Discussion, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Experimental Evaluation
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: A Computer-Based Driver Improvement System, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Driver Improvement Clinic Induces Attitude Change by Group Discussion, 05/1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: A Group Discussion Technique for Violators, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Programmed Teaching, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    an aid to driver education
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Driver Improvement or System Improvement, 01/1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Traffic Safety Research Review, 02/1964 --03/1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Journal of Safety Research, 03/1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Driver Behavior Research Project: Traffic Digest and Review, 05/1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Report for RRC, 04/30/1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    #12 Mid-East Regional Resource Center
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Report for RRC, 01/31/1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly and Final Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 02/1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 05/1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 08/1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 11/1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 02/1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 05/1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 08/1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Resource Center: Quarterly Overview of RRC Progress, 11/1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: NASA Briefing Session Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology, 03/17/1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Final Report-Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology, 10/20/1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Interdependencies Between Civilian and Military Interests in and Responsibilities for the Advancement of New Technologies
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: First Quarterly Report, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Trends in Western Political and Economic Policies
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Second Quarterly Report, 12/1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    The Prevention and Control of Delinquency and Crime
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Report of the Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology, 04/15/1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Contractor's Report, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    HUD Tasks 1 and 2
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Interim Report, 09/1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Program of Policy Studies and Technology
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: First Quarterly Report, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Innovation Information and Analysis Project
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Mid-Year Report, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Annual Report, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: GWU Science and Technology Publications, 08/1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Innovation Information Center, 06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Book List
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Innovation Information and Analysis Project, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Book List 3
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Innovation Information and Analysis Project, 07/1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Book List 4
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Behavioral Aspects of Innovation, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Selected Bibliography Part I
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: Publications, Reports, Books, 09/1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology, 12/1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    The Public Policy Dimensions of Artificial Insemination and Human-Semen Cryobanking
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: The Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    A Model for Legislative Reform?
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology: A Comparison of the United States and Soviet Space Programs, 06/1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Program of Policy Studies in Science and Technology, 05/1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Proposal for the Development and Implementation of a Behavioral Systems Approach to the Prevention and Control of Delinquency and Crime
  - Institute for Educational Leadership: A Search for New Energy, 06/1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership: Report on Institutional Eligibility, 06/1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership: Institute for Educational Leadership's report to The Ford Foundation, 11/1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    2 copies
  - Institute for Educational Leadership: Report on the Ford Fellows in Educational Journalism, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Pilot Program, Volumes I and II
  - Institute for Educational Leadership: Annual Evaluation Report, 09/1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    The Career Education Project
  - Institute for Educational Leadership: Interim Report, 06/1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    ASE Contract
  - Institute for Educational Leadership, 12/1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    An Essay on Federal Incentives and Local and State Educational Initiatives
  - Sex Roles Issues of Minority Women, 05/1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership, 03/08/1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Two photos-John Merrow and Wendy Blair, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Co-hosts of NPR's weekly "Options in Education"
  - Options in Education, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Report on Grant of the Carnegie Corporation for "Options in Education", 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bach, Stark and Associates, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Report of Activities in the Educational Staff, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Seminar
  - Interim Report of the Family Impact, 06/1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Family Impact Analysis, 11/1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Juvenile Court Dependency Hearings and Related Policies in Bellingham Washington
  - Family Impact Analysis: A Community Perspective, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Social Research Group: American Drinking Practices, 10/11/1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Social Research Group: Studies of Drinking Practices, 1962-1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Social Research Group: Final report, 1966-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Longitudinal Study of Educationally Disadvantaged Students in DC Public Schools
  - Social Research Group: Tables and References, 09/15/1968 --09/20/1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Differences in Sub-Group Drinking Patterns in a US National Survey
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of the Emergency Care Program, 06/1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Acute Alcohol Intoxication at the Detoxification Center
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of the Emergency Care Program, 09/1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of the Programs in DC under ESEA Title I, 12/1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of the Programs in DC under ESEA Title I, 06/1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Social Research Group: Research Design, 02/1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Staffing Guide for Army Libraries and Information Facilities
  - Social Research Group, 12/1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    A Study of the Effectiveness of Selected Out-Of-School Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs
  - Social Research Group, 09/1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Analysis of the Teacher Aide Program in Title I Schools School Year 1969-1970
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of Programs in the District of Columbia Under ESEA Title I, 03/1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of Programs in the District of Columbia Under ESEA Title I, 01/1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Social Research Group: Marijuana Use Among Adults in a Large City and Suburb, 05/1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of Programs in the District of Columbia Under ESEA Title I, 04/1971 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Social Research Group: Broad Agency Goals and Agency Research Objectives for 1972, 12/1971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Social Research Group: Legislative Mandates for Early Childhood Research, 12/1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Social Research Group: Early Childhood Research and Development, 02/1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Needs, Gaps, and Imbalances
  - Social Research Group: A Statement and Working Paper on Longitudinal, 04/1972 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Social Research Group: The Socialization of Youth for Work, 06/1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Social Research Group: An Analysis of the Longitudinal, 12/1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Intervention Research Funded by Member Agencies of the Interagency Panel on Early Childhood Research and Development
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of ESEA Title I Programs for DC, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Social Research Group: Organization and Function of the Support System, 04/1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Interagency Panels for Early Childhood Research and Development on Adolescence
  - Social Research Group: Societal Change and Rate of Research Progress, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Social Research Group: Inter-agency Panel on Early Childhood Research and Development, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Social Research Group: In Furtherance of Cumulative Knowledge, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    NIMH Initiatives
  - Social Research Group: A Progress Report on Developing Comparability in Research, 09/1974 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Social Research Group: Towards Comparability in Family Research, 11/1974 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Analysis of Comparability Potential and Information on OCD Research Projects on the Family
  - Social Research Group: Draft on Policy Guidelines for Information Release, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Social Research Group: Grant, Contract, and Program Proposals, 02/1975 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Instructions
  - Social Research Group: Towards More Comparability and Generalizability of Developmental Research, 04/1975 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Social Research Group: Evaluation of Programs in DC under ESEA Title I, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Social Research Group: Towards Comparability in Family Research II, 01/1976 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Analysis of Comparability Potential and Information on 1975
  - Biometric Laboratory, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Chemistry, 1970-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    For Air Force, Office of Naval Research
  - Education Research Project, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rehabilitation Research and Training Center, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Hospital
  - Medical Center: "Beware the Wind", 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Regarding air pollution
  - Natural Resources Policy Center, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Manpower Research Projects, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Science: Joint Institute for Advancement of Flight Sciences, 06/1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Program of Research in Laminar Flow Control in the JIAFS at NASA Langley Research Center
  - School of Engineering and Applied Science: Annual Summary Report, 06/01/1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Science: Proving the Correctness of the Flight Director Program, 07/1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Volumes I and III
  - School of Engineering and Applied Science: The Core-Flow Rotary Jet, 06/1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    A Preliminary Analysis, Part I
  - Graduate Program in Science, Technology, and Public Policy: The Second Five-Year Outlook, 01/1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Final Report Phase I: Evaluation and Issues for the Future
  - Center for Transnational Management Development, 08/30/1978 --09/01/1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    International Management Courses of the Center for Transnational Management Development Financed by the Associate Directorate for Educational and Cultural Affairs of the International Communication Agency during the period
  - Medical Center: Annual Report, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center: Annual Report, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Medical Center: Health Care Financing Administration, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Army Logistics: Research Study Report, 11/1959 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    4 Evaluation of the Logistics Command Management System
  - Army Logistics: The Transportation Corps, 04/1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Research Study Report 6
  - Army Logistics: Transportation Research Studies, 06/1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Report 9
  - Army Logistics: Transportation Research Studies, 09/1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Report 11
  - Army Logistics: Transportation Research Studies, 05/1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Report 13